<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Customer>
	<Customer>
		<Title>Glendalough half day</Title>
		<Area>Wicklow</Area>
		<StudentCost>€4.00</StudentCost>
		<Transport>Yes</Transport>
    <Transport16>€225.00</Transport16>
    <Transport30>€330.00</Transport30>
    <Transport53>€370.00</Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>http://www.glendalough.ie/</Website>
    <Information>For thousands of years people have been drawn to ‘the valley of the two lakes‘ for its spectacular scenery, rich history, archaeology and abundant wildlife. 
    Glendalough is a remarkable place that will still your mind, inspire your heart and fill your soul.</Information>
	</Customer>
  <Customer>
    <Title>Glendalough full day</Title>
    <Area>Wicklow</Area>
    <StudentCost>€4.00</StudentCost>
    <Transport>Yes</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30>€410.00</Transport30>
    <Transport53>€490.00</Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>http://www.glendalough.ie/</Website>
  <Information>For thousands of years people have been drawn to ‘the valley of the two lakes‘ for its spectacular scenery, rich history, archaeology and abundant wildlife. 
    Glendalough is a remarkable place that will still your mind, inspire your heart and fill your soul.</Information>
  </Customer>
  <Customer>
    <Title>Ardgillan Castle</Title>
    <Area>Co. Dublin</Area>
    <StudentCost>€5.50</StudentCost>
    <Transport>Yes</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30>€370.00</Transport30>
    <Transport53>€530.00</Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>http://ardgillancastle.ie//</Website>
    <Information>Ardgillan Castle and Demesne is Ireland’s hidden gem. 
    Set in spectacular parklands overlooking the Irish Sea with a magnificent view of the Mourne Mountains. 
    As well as the castle, the demesne features a walled and rose garden both of which present an orderly profusion of colour.</Information>
  </Customer>
  <Customer>
    <Title>Aviva Stadium</Title>
    <Area>Dublin</Area>
    <StudentCost>€9.50</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>www.avivastadium.ie/</Website>
    <Information>Did you know that Aviva Stadium was built on one of the oldest sports grounds in the world? 
Did you know that the first ever international athletic meeting happened on Lansdowne Road in 1876?
Want to learn more about our 150 years of Irish Sporting History? Visit us for a tour. 
You will see the press conference room, home dressing rooms, players' tunnel, dugouts and more. 
Our tour guides will bring you around the stadium and entertain you for an hour.</Information>
  </Customer>
  <Customer>
    <Title>Battle of the Boyne Visitor Centre</Title>
    <Area>Drogheda</Area>
    <StudentCost>€4.50</StudentCost>
    <Transport>Yes</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30>€370.00</Transport30>
    <Transport53>€530.00</Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>http://www.battleoftheboyne.ie/</Website>
    <Information>The Battle of the Boyne is one of the most significant events in Irish history.

The Battle of the Boyne was fought between King William III and his father-in-law King James II on 1 July 1690. 
The kings were rival claimants to the English, Scottish and Irish thrones. 
Protestant King William (of Orange) had deposed Catholic King James in 1688.</Information>
  </Customer>
  <Customer>
    <Title>Book of Kells</Title>
    <Area>Dublin</Area>
    <StudentCost>Oct-Mar:€3.50, Apr-Sep:€9.50</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>https://www.tcd.ie/visitors/book-of-kells/</Website>
    <Information>The Book of Kells is Ireland's greatest cultural treasure and the world's most famous medieval manuscript. 
    
  The 9th century book is a richly decorated copy of the four Gospels of the life of Jesus Christ.</Information>
  </Customer>
  <Customer>
    <Title>Bray Bowl</Title>
    <Area>Bray</Area>
    <StudentCost>1 game of Bowling: €27.00 per lane (max 6 per lane).  For the 'All-in Deal', this is €13.00 per student.</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>http://www.braybowl.ie/</Website>
    <Information>There is so much to do at Bray Bowl, with 16 tenpin bowling lanes, 
an arcade, snooker and pool and Quasar laser tag arena!</Information>
  </Customer>
  <Customer>
    <Title>Bray Head Walk</Title>
    <Area>Bray</Area>
    <StudentCost>Free</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website></Website>
    <Information>To get some of the most stunning views of Bray, look no further than Bray Head. 
    The hill dominates the end of the promenade and the stone cross atop the hill is an iconic feature of the town.
    While the climb is not particularly daunting, some parts can be a bit of a challenge and require some scrambling. 
    But if the hike up doesn’t leave you breathless the views sure will!</Information>
  </Customer>
  <Customer>
    <Title>Butlers Chocolate Experience</Title>
    <Area>Dublin</Area>
    <StudentCost>€13.00</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>http://www.butlerschocolates.com/chocolateexperience</Website>
    <Information>Visit the Butlers Chocolate Experience - the ultimate chocolate discovery tour in Ireland. 
    Based in the home of Ireland's favourite chocolates, a visit here is a must for chocolate lovers of all ages.</Information>
  </Customer>
  <Customer>
    <Title>Causey Farm Half Day</Title>
    <Area>Co. Meath</Area>
    <StudentCost>€15.00</StudentCost>
    <Transport>Yes</Transport>
    <Transport16>€225.00</Transport16>
    <Transport30>€290.00</Transport30>
    <Transport53>€370.00</Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>http://www.causey.ie/</Website>
    <Information>Causey Farm is a fun based venue for a variety of entertainment, tourism and educational programs. 
We provide interactive cultural experiences in a friendly atmosphere for Irish and international groups, 
as well as fantastic seasonal events for families and individuals.
Our educational programs have an interactive, ‘Hands-On’ focus, visitors get to participate in all activities. 
For international tourists – learn about live Irish culture the fun way! Dance a jig, play the bodhráin, 
cut turf in a bog, bake brown soda bread, see a sheepdog at work and more!</Information>
  </Customer>
  <Customer>
    <Title>Causey Farm Full Day</Title>
    <Area>Co. Meath</Area>
    <StudentCost>€20.00</StudentCost>
    <Transport>Yes</Transport>
    <Transport16>€345.00</Transport16>
    <Transport30>€410.00</Transport30>
    <Transport53>€490.00</Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>http://www.causey.ie/</Website>
  <Information>Causey Farm is a fun based venue for a variety of entertainment, tourism and educational programs. 
We provide interactive cultural experiences in a friendly atmosphere for Irish and international groups, 
as well as fantastic seasonal events for families and individuals.
Our educational programs have an interactive, ‘Hands-On’ focus, visitors get to participate in all activities. 
For international tourists – learn about live Irish culture the fun way! Dance a jig, play the bodhráin, 
cut turf in a bog, bake brown soda bread, see a sheepdog at work and more!</Information>
  </Customer>
<Customer>
    <Title>Ceilí Irish Dancing</Title>
    <Area>Co. Dublin</Area>
    <StudentCost>€10.00</StudentCost>
    <Transport>Optional</Transport>
    <Transport16>One way: €200.00, Two way: €250.00</Transport16>
    <Transport30>One way: €270.00, Two way: €310.00</Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>https://comhaltas.ie/</Website>
  <Information>Our Céilí takes place on a Friday night at 9pm until midnight. 
  Music is provided by a live Céilí band featuring instruments such as fiddle, tin whistle, flute, accordion, 
  bodhrán, producing Ireland’s unique traditional rhythmical sound that encourages feet and fingers to tap. 
  We also provide a “Caller”, a person that calls out the dance steps as the music is played, so even complete beginners can join in. 
  Entrance to the Céilí will cost you €10 and includes tea/coffee and scone.</Information>
  </Customer>
<Customer>
    <Title>Chester Beatty Library</Title>
    <Area>Dublin</Area>
    <StudentCost>Free</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>http://www.cbl.ie/</Website>
  <Information>With free admission and described by the Lonely Planet as not just the best museum in Dublin, 
  but one of the best in Europe, the Chester Beatty Library is a must-see on any Dublin visitor's itinerary.  
  As the only museum in Ireland to win 'European Museum of the Year' and rated consistently in the top 5 of TripAdvisor’s list of ‘Top things to do in Dublin', 
  the library's rich collections from countries across Asia, the Middle East, North Africa and Europe open a window on the artistic treasures of the great cultures and religions of the world.</Information>
  </Customer>
<Customer>
    <Title>Christchurch Cathedral</Title>
    <Area>Dublin</Area>
    <StudentCost>€4.50</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>http://christchurchcathedral.ie/</Website>
  <Information>Christ Church Cathedral (founded c.1028) is the spiritual heart of the city, and one of the top visitor attractions in Dublin. 
  Step inside and you can enjoy the cathedral’s beautiful interior and fascinating medieval crypt.</Information>
  </Customer>
<Customer>
    <Title>Greystones Cliff Walk</Title>
    <Area>Bray</Area>
    <StudentCost>Free (Guided: €2.00)</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>http://visitwicklow.ie/activities/cliff-walk-bray-to-greystones/</Website>
  <Information>The Cliff Walk from Bray to Greystones is one of Bray’s most popular attractions, for both visitors and locals alike. 
  The coastal walk winds along the side of Bray Head and has some of the most stunning views of the East Coast.

The Cliff Walk is about 7 kilometres, starting from the bandstand on the Promenade and ending at Greystones harbour. 
The walk takes about 2 hours to complete and is suitable for all abilities. The Cliff Walk follows the rail line so 
you can conveniently return to Bray on the Dart retracing your steps and reliving the view from the comfort of the train!

The Cliff Walk is home to numerous types of seabirds and various types of colourful wildflowers that add to the natural beauty of the walk. 
The keen observer also might spot dolphins, black harbour porpoises and basking sharks swimming in the waters around the Cliff.</Information>
  </Customer>
<Customer>
    <Title>Clonmacnoise</Title>
    <Area>Co. Offaly</Area>
    <StudentCost>€4.50</StudentCost>
    <Transport>Yes</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>http://www.heritageireland.ie/en/midlands-eastcoast/clonmacnoise/</Website>
  <Information>An Early Christian site founded by St. Ciarán in the mid-6th century on the eastern bank of the River Shannon. 
  The site includes the ruins of a cathedral, seven churches (10th  -13th century), two round towers, three high crosses and the largest collection of Early Christian graveslabs in Western Europe. 
  The original high crosses and a selection of graveslabs are on display in the visitor centre.
The long and varied history of Clonmacnoise is recounted in an audiovisual presentation shown in the visitor centre. 
There are also exhibitions that deal with the flora, fauna and landscape of the region.</Information>
  </Customer>
<Customer>
    <Title>Collins Barracks Museum</Title>
    <Area>Dublin</Area>
    <StudentCost>Free</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>http://www.museum.ie/Decorative-Arts-History</Website>
  <Information>The National Museum of Ireland - Decorative Arts and History is a branch of the National Museum of Ireland 
  located at the former Collins Barracks in the Arbour Hill area of Dublin, Ireland. 
  The main focus of the galleries is on arts, craft and wares, including exhibits on: 
  Irish coins and currency, 
  silverware, 
  furniture, 
  folklife and costumes, 
  ceramics, 
  and glassware. 
  Included are artifacts such as Etruscan vases, gauntlets worn by King William at the Battle of the Boyne, 
  a life belt and oar salvaged from the wreck of the RMS Lusitania and a pocket book carried by Wolfe Tone whilst imprisoned in the Barracks.</Information>
  </Customer>
<Customer>
    <Title>Croke Park GAA Museum</Title>
    <Area>Dublin</Area>
    <StudentCost>Museum/Stand: €8.00, Museum/Stadium: €9.00</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>https://crokepark.ie/gaa-museum-tours/gaa-museum</Website>
  <Information>Get ready to immerse yourself in the spine-tingling and completely unique story of Gaelic games from ancient times to the present day. 

This museum is like no other sporting museum you’ll ever visit. 
It not only celebrates the history of Ireland’s national games, it also vividly brings to life how the GAA has contributed to our cultural, social and sporting heritage. </Information>
  </Customer>
<Customer>
    <Title>Dalkey Castle</Title>
    <Area>Co. Dublin</Area>
    <StudentCost>€7.00</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>http://www.dalkeycastle.com/</Website>
  <Information>Dalkey Castle in Dublin includes many living history actors who show 
  visitors skills and cultural features from the 1500s in Ireland – such as 
  an archer shooting a longbow, a cook making hedgehog pie and a barber surgeon offering haircuts.

Panoramic views of sea and mountains can be seen from the castle battlements. 
Visitors can also explore the early Christian church and graveyard, dedicated to St. Begnet.</Information>
  </Customer>
<Customer>
    <Title>Dublin Castle</Title>
    <Area>Dublin</Area>
    <StudentCost>€7.50</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>http://www.dublincastle.ie/</Website>
  <Information>Erected in the early thirteenth century on the site of a Viking settlement, 
  Dublin Castle served for centuries as the headquarters of English, and later British, administration in Ireland. 
  In 1922, following Ireland’s independence, Dublin Castle was handed over to the new Irish government. 
  It is now a major government complex and a key tourist attraction.</Information>
  </Customer>
<Customer>
    <Title>Dublin Writers Museum</Title>
    <Area>Dublin</Area>
    <StudentCost>€5.00</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website></Website>
  <Information>The Irish literary tradition is one of the most illustrious in the world, 
  famous for four Nobel Prize winners and for many other writers of international renown. 

In 1991, the Dublin Writers Museum was opened to house a history and celebration of literary Dublin. 

Situated in a magnificent 18th century mansion in the north city centre, 
the collection features the lives and works of Dublin's literary celebrities over the past three hundred years. </Information>
  </Customer>
<Customer>
    <Title>Dublin Zoo</Title>
    <Area>Dublin</Area>
    <StudentCost>Under 16: €11.00. Over 16: €16.00</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>https://www.dublinzoo.ie/</Website>
  <Information>Dublin Zoo is much more than a fun-filled, stimulating day out for all the family... 
  it’s a place to learn about wild animals, especially those which are endangered. 
  The Zoo is a registered charity – your visit will help maintain Dublin Zoo to a high standard, improve the Zoo and contribute to conservation programmes.  

Located in the Phoenix Park in the heart of Dublin city, Dublin Zoo is Ireland’s most popular family attraction, and welcomed over one million visitors last year. 

As one of the world’s oldest, yet popular zoos, the 28 hectare park in the heart of Dublin is home to some 400 animals in safe environment where education and 
conservation combine for an exciting and unforgettable experience!</Information>
  </Customer>
<Customer>
    <Title>Dublinia Viking Exhibition</Title>
    <Area>Dublin</Area>
    <StudentCost>€5.50</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>http://www.dublinia.ie/</Website>
  <Information>Dublinia is located at the crossroads of the medieval city at Christchurch, where modern and old Dublin meet. 
  Dublinia is history brought to life in an exciting way for all to engage, learn and share. With our four exciting exhibitions, 
  you can visit Viking and Medieval Dublin, see Archaeology as a History Hunter and climb the medieval St Michael’s Tower. 
  At Dublinia, see Dublin from a new perspective and come away knowing more about its citizens throughout the ages!</Information>
  </Customer>
<Customer>
    <Title>Dublinia and Christchurch</Title>
    <Area>Dublin</Area>
    <StudentCost>€9.00</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>http://www.dublinia.ie/</Website>
  <Information></Information>
  </Customer>
<Customer>
    <Title>DunLaoghaire Maritime Museum</Title>
    <Area>Co. Dublin</Area>
    <StudentCost>€6.00</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>http://www.mariner.ie/?gclid=CIOA1faX0tYCFWS37QodG-YMsQ</Website>
  <Information>Ireland’s National Maritime Museum is housed in Dun Laoghaire’s 180-year-old Mariners Church, 
  directly opposite the new DLR Lexicon library and easily accessible by DART suburban train and several bus services. 
  The museum’s greatest artefact is probably the building itself as it is one of a few custom built places of worship for seafarers remaining intact in the world to-day.

Experienced guides will bring you on a voyage of discovery enthralling you with stories of discovery, heroism, war and disasters at sea. 
You will learn about maritime history, exploration, navigation, radio, deep-sea cable technology, nature, wildlife and view art inspired by the sea.

See the 10-tonne revolving Baily Optic, try the electrified steam engine and pause to reflect at the Titanic exhibit, 
the re-created radio room, the Royal Navy prisoners docks and the war memorial. 
Try sailor’s knots, learn how they lift heavy weights, be photographed with the pirate, research in the library, 
visit the shop and café and much more.</Information>
  </Customer>
<Customer>
    <Title>Dunmore Caves</Title>
    <Area>Co. Kilkenny</Area>
    <StudentCost>€4.50</StudentCost>
    <Transport>Yes</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>https://www.irelandsancienteast.com/discover/stories/featured-stories/dunmore-cave?gclid=EAIaIQobChMI-c2UrJjS1gIVzJ0bCh1xsAYtEAAYASAAEgIZ4fD_BwE</Website>
  <Information>History and geology blend at Dunmore Cave to give an interesting and unique situation. 
  Consisting of a series of chambers formed over millions of years, the cave contains some of the finest calcite formations found in any Irish cave. 
  The cave has been known to man for many centuries and is first mentioned in the 9th century Irish Triads. The most interesting reference however, 
  comes from the Annals which tells of a Viking massacre at the cave in the year 928 A.D.  
  Archaeological finds within the cave confirm Viking activity. 
  Exhibitions and displays in the Visitor Centre. 
  
The cave is inaccessible for wheelchair users.</Information>
  </Customer>
<Customer>
    <Title>EPIC Ireland</Title>
    <Area>Dublin</Area>
    <StudentCost>€9.00</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>http://epicchq.com/</Website>
  <Information>Our family-friendly state of the art museum is suitable for all ages. 
  Cutting-edge interactive technology brings visitors on a journey through the Irish emigration experience, 
  acquainting them with the influence the Irish have brought to bear worldwide in the areas of sport, culture, art, politics, activism, charity, science, and many more. 
  The exhibition is made up of twenty galleries which are each individually themed, and fall under the headings of 
  Migration (Galleries 1-2), 
  Motivation (Galleries 4-7), 
  Influence (Galleries 8-18) 
  and Diaspora Today (Galleries 19-20). 
  EPIC is located in the restored vaults of CHQ in Dublin’s Custom House Quarter. 
  It was officially opened on May 6th 2016 by founder Neville Isdell and former President of Ireland Mary Robinson. 
  EPIC aims to reflect the past, and to invite visitors from across the globe to discover heretofore unknown connections.</Information>
  </Customer>
  <Customer>
    <Title>Glasnevin Cemetery</Title>
    <Area>Dublin</Area>
    <StudentCost>Under 18: €7.00,
    Over 18: €8.00</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>https://www.glasnevinmuseum.ie/index.cfm</Website>
    <Information>Glasnevin Cemetery Museum, both the guardian and storyteller for over 1.5 million people. 
    From the ordinary to the truly extraordinary, these people helped shape the Ireland of today. 
    We want to share their stories and times with you through tours of the cemetery, 
    a visit to the museum or through a genealogy search for your family history.</Information>
  </Customer>
  <Customer>
    <Title>Guinness Storehouse</Title>
    <Area>Dublin</Area>
    <StudentCost>Under 18: €13.00, Over 18: €14.50</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>1 free per 15 students</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€14.50</LeaderCost>
    <Website>https://www.guinness-storehouse.com/en</Website>
    <Information>Located in the heart of the St. James's Gate Brewery, the Guinness Storehouse® is Ireland's most popular tourist attraction. 
    It's the home of the Black Stuff, the heart of Dublin and an unforgettable start to your Irish adventure.

The journey begins at the bottom of the world's largest pint glass and continues up through seven floors filled with interactive 
experiences that fuse our long brewing heritage with Ireland's rich history. 
At the top, you'll be rewarded with a pint of perfection in our world-famous rooftop Gravity Bar. 
Now that's our kind of higher education.</Information>
  </Customer>
  <Customer>
    <Title>Hill of Tara</Title>
    <Area>Co. Meath</Area>
    <StudentCost>Free</StudentCost>
    <Transport>Yes</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>http://hilloftara.org/</Website>
    <Information>The Hill of Tara, located near the River Boyne, is an archaeological complex that runs between Navan and Dunshaughlin in County Meath, Leinster, Ireland. 
    It contains a number of ancient monuments, and, according to tradition, was the seat of Árd Rí na hÉireann, or the High King of Ireland. 
    Recent scholarship claims that despite the rich narratives derived from mythologies, 
    Tara was not so much a true seat of kingship, but a sacral site associated with kingship rituals.</Information>
  </Customer>
  <Customer>
    <Title>Howth</Title>
    <Area>Co. Dublin</Area>
    <StudentCost>Free</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website>http://www.visitdublin.com/hooked-on-howth-dublin</Website>
    <Information>Below the hilly headland at the northern boundary of Dublin Bay lies the small fishing village of Howth. 
    There are so many things to do in Howth – an angler’s dream; cod and ray are commonly caught here as fishing trawlers weave in and out of the harbour. 
    All the while, restaurants along the seafront serve up the catch of the day to hungry hikers fresh off the Howth Head walk...</Information>
  </Customer>
  <Customer>
    <Title>Bray Irish Dancing</Title>
    <Area>Bray</Area>
    <StudentCost>€9.50</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website></Website>
    <Information>Irish dance lessons take place in Bray, generally in the Esplanade Hotel, but can also be held in the Martello Hotel.
    Over an hour and a half, the students are given expert lessons in traditional Irish dancing.
  Good exercise and lots of fun!</Information>
  </Customer>
<Customer>
    <Title>Bray Irish Dancing</Title>
    <Area>Bray</Area>
    <StudentCost>€9.50</StudentCost>
    <Transport>No</Transport>
    <Transport16></Transport16>
    <Transport30></Transport30>
    <Transport53></Transport53>
    <LeaderFree>Yes</LeaderFree>
    <LeaderCost>€0.00</LeaderCost>
    <Website></Website>
    <Information>Irish dance lessons take place in Bray, generally in the Esplanade Hotel, but can also be held in the Martello Hotel.
    Over an hour and a half, the students are given expert lessons in traditional Irish dancing.
  Good exercise and lots of fun!</Information>
  </Customer>
</Customer>